NICHOLAS ROSALES

CONTACT

Address : Tucson, AZ 85747 **Phone :** 520-437-9590

Email: nickjrosales@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Experienced in Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, React, Express.js, and GraphQL.
- Created full stack applications, including a user based fitness application.
- Worked on teams to develop different applications.
- Presented my final project at Demo Day to different industry professionals.

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://github.com/nickrosales
- https://nickrosales.github.io/reactportfolio/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/nickrosales/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Through my work experiences I've developed excellent collaboration skills. These were further expanded through working with multiple team members on different full stack projects and enhanced my abilities to work on challenges as a team. I have outstanding attention to detail, with a high capacity to stick to deadlines and problem solve. I'm passionate about pursuing a career that will let me expand my skill set.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, 05/2023 The University of Arizona

240 Program hours

Supplemental Educational Courses Pima Community College

System Administration, Networking, Cyber Security, Linux/Unix, And Python

Volunteer Experience

HIPAA Compliance Requirements
Any Lab Test Now Medical Assistant Certification Program
Department of Transportation (DOT) Drug Testing

WORK HISTORY

FACILITY MANAGER – MEDICAL ASSISTANT/PHLEBOTOMIST, 05/2017 to Current

ANY LAB TEST NOW

- Supervisor: Lauri Wallner, Owner, (520) 444-7439
- Modified location practices to ensure compliance with federal and state regulations, including Health Insurance Portability and Accountability ACT (HIPAA) and Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA)
- Worked with customers to select medical tests and performed necessary medical collections.

KITCHEN MANAGER, 04/2015 to 05/2017 CHIPOTLE

• Supervisor: Kristen, General Manager, (520) 203-0004

SALON COORDINATOR, 09/2010 to 01/2013 Metropolis

• Supervisor: Emery Nicoletti, Owner, (520) 237-3412